Some days you're the only thing I know Only thing that's burning when the nights
grow cold Can't look away, can't look away
Beg you to stay, beg you to stay, yeah Sometimes you're a stranger in my bed
Don't know if you love me or you want me dead
Push me away, push me away Beg me to stay, beg me to stay, yeah
Call me in the morning to apologize Every little eye gives me butterflies
Something in the wind looking through my eyes Don't know if I'm gonna make it out alive
Fight so dirty but your love's so sweet Talk so pretty but you're a party
Late night devil put your hands on me And never, never, never, ever let go
Some days you're the best thing in my life Sometimes when I look at you I see my wife
And you're down into somebody I don't know And you push me away, push me away, yeah
Call me in the morning to apologize Every little eye gives me butterflies
Something in the wind looking through my eyes Don't know if I'm gonna make it out alive
Fight so dirty but your love's so sweet Talk so pretty but you're a party
Late night devil put your hands on me And never, never, never, ever let go
Blood on my shirt, rose in my hand You're looking at me like you don't know who I am
Blood on my shirt, heart in my hand Still I'll be there
Fight so dirty but your love's so sweet Talk so pretty but you're a party
Late night devil put your hands on me And never, never, never, ever let go
Never, never, never, ever let go
Lyrics by TheBetta