I remember years ago someone told me I should take caution when it comes to love
I did, I did
You were strong and I was not my illusion, my mistake
I was careless, I forgot I did, I did
And now, when all is done there is nothing to say
You have gone, it's a effortless slate
You have won, you can go ahead tell them
Show them all I know now
Shout it from the roaches
I've landed on the skyline
All we had is gone now
Show them I was happy
And my heart is broken
All my scars are open
Tell them what I hope will be
Impossible, impossible, impossible, impossible
Falling out of love is hard
Falling for betraying's worth
Broken trust and broken hearts
I know, I know
Thinking all you need is there
Building faith, all love and word
Empty promises will wear
I know, I know
And now, when all is gone there is nothing to say
And if you're done with embarrassing me
On your own you can go ahead tell them
Tell them all I know now
Shout it from the rooftops
I've landed on the skyline
All we had is gone now
Tell them I was happy
And my heart is broken
All my scars are open
Tell them what I hope would be
Impossible, impossible, impossible, impossible
Impossible, impossible, impossible
I remember years ago
Someone told me I should take caution
When it comes to love I didn't
Tell them all I know now
Shout it from the rooftops
I've landed on the skyline
All we had is gone now
Tell them I was happy
And my heart is broken
All my scars are open
They'll live a life of what I've been
Impossible, impossible, impossible
Impossible
I remember years ago
Someone told me I should take caution
When it comes to love I didn't
Tell them I was happy