Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
This is everything I did and I
Wave, don't tell me Heaven is a place on Earth
I wish I could rewind all the times that I didn't Show you what you really were
What you really were
Wave, you held me I wish that I put you first
I was wrong, I admit, numb from the kids While you were slipping through my fingertips
Taking every breath away With all of the mistakes I've made
From all the letters that I've made This is everything I didn't say
I wish I could have made you stay And I'm the only one to blame
I know that it's a little too late This is everything I didn't say
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
This is everything I did and I
Wake me up now And tell me this is all a bad dream
All the songs that I wrote, all the wrongs That I hoped would erase from your memory
I'm a man of fear
Oh, teen or two A broken and empty heart
If that was I, I should have fought all the hours I lost Wish I could bring it back to the start
Taking every breath away With all of the mistakes I've made
From all the letters that I've made This is everything I didn't say
I wish I could have made you stay And I'm the only one to blame
I know that it's a little too late This is everything I didn't say
I hope you know You are just right
To make this right, whoa, whoa
Someday I'll be sure To pass each other by
Until that time
Taking every breath away With all of the mistakes I've made
From all the letters that I've made This is everything I didn't say
I wish I could have made you stay And I'm the only one to blame
I know that it's a little too late This is everything I didn't say
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
This is everything I didn't say Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh