Those hardest to love needed most I watched our bodies turn to ghosts
Such good friends it has to end, it always does
The way life is, do we take that risk?
And so it all boils down to this We've got our aim but we might miss
We are too fragile just to guess And I've been in this place before
We'll find out who we are but we want more That's human nature at its best
What if we ruin it all? And we love like fools
And do what we have, we lose And I don't want you to go but I want you so
So tell me what we choose
Friends, I watched as as we changed The feelings in my headspace rearranged
I want you more than I've wanted, anyone? Isn't that dangerous?
The anticipation before the kiss Mirrored in my shaking lips
Oh God, I feel so unprepared The two of us so out of place
My feelings written on my face Got what I want but now I'm scared
What if we ruin it all? And we love like fools
And do what we have, we lose And I don't want you to go but I want you so
So tell me what, tell me what we choose What we choose, what we choose
What if we ruin it all? And we love like fools
And do what we have, we lose And I don't want you to go but I want you so
So tell me what, tell me what, tell me what we choose