Legends never die When the world is calling you
Can you hear them screaming out your name?
Legends never die They become a part of you
Every time you bleed far reaching Greatness, relentless, you survive
They never lose hope When everything's cold and the fighting's near
It's deep in their bones They'll ride into smoke when the fire is fierce
Oh, pick yourself up, cause Legends never die
When the world is calling you Can you hear them screaming out your name?
Legends never die They become a part of you
Every time you bleed far reaching Greatness, the legends never die
They're written down in eternity But you'll never see the price you've cost
The scars collected all their lives When everything's lost, they pick up their hearts and avenge defeat
Before it all starts, they suffer through harm just to touch the dream
Oh, pick yourself up, cause Legends never die
When the world is calling you Can you hear them screaming out your name?
Legends never die They become a part of you
Every time you bleed far reaching Greatness, the legends never die
When the world is calling out your name I beg of you to fight
Pick yourself up once more Pick yourself up five times
Legends never die When the world is calling you
Can you hear them screaming out your name? Legends never die
They become a part of you Every time you bleed far reaching
Greatness, the legends never die
Thanks for watching!