["I Want to Take You Somewhere"]
I wanna take you somewhere, so you know I care
But it's so cold and I don't know where
I brought you daffodils and a pretty string
But they won't flower like the flowers spring
And I wanna kiss you, make you feel alright
I'm just so tired to share my nights
I wanna cry and I wanna love
But all my tears have been used up
On another love, another love
All my tears have been used up
And if somebody hurts you, I wanna fight
But my hand's been broken one too many times
So I use my voice, I'll be so fucking rude
Watch they always win, but I know I'll lose
And I'd sing a song that'd be just stars
But I sang a love to another heart
And I wanna cry, I wanna love to love
But all my tears have been used up
On another love, another love
All my tears have been used up
Oh, oh
I wanna sing a song that'd be just stars
But I sang a love to another heart
And I wanna cry, I wanna fall in love
But all my tears have been used up
On another love, another love
All my tears have been used up