You said that we would always be Without you I feel lost at sea
Through the darkness you'd hide with me Like the wind we'd be wild and free
You said you'd follow me anywhere Through your eyes
Tell me you won't be there
I gotta learn how to love without you I gotta carry my cross without you
I'm stuck in the middle and I'm just about to Figure it out without you
And I'm not sitting on without you Fuck I'm blowing up without you
I'm gonna tear this city down without you I'm going body in clouds without you
Now I'm running, moving my dear From myself and the truth I fear
My heart is beating, I can't see clear How I'm wishing that you were here
You said you'd follow me anywhere Through your eyes
Tell me you won't be there
I gotta learn how to love without you I gotta carry my cross without you
I'm stuck in the middle and I'm just about to Figure it out without you
And I'm not sitting on without you Fuck I'm blowing up without you
I'm gonna tear this city down without you I'm going body in clouds without you
I'm not sitting on without you