So this woman was on a train in New Jersey.
Let's call her Tipsy.
And all of a sudden, Tipsy overhears some guys talking trash about her.
These guys, who we'll call the Germans.
Now I don't know if they were actually talking trash about her,
but Tipsy believes they are and she doesn't like it one bit.
No! Tell me why the f*** you guys...
He's so f***ing scared of my son.
Please...
Now Tipsy, she's on the train with this guy.
And it's unclear if he's her boyfriend or her husband,
so we'll just call him Busbund.
Now Busbund, he doesn't think the Germans said anything.
I can handle my own.
Breathe. Stop this or I'm never gonna talk to them.
And here's where it all goes downhill.
She suddenly figures out that they aren't from the US.
How about you get the f*** out of our country?
Do not!
How come my f***ing ambushes speak of last words?
And poor Busbund, he's just over here trying to de-escalate.
I'm an immigrant. You know I'm an immigrant too. You know that, right?
But I'm a citizen of the US, so it's okay.
Oh, but there's more.
So this whole exchange gets recorded and uploaded to Reddit.
And people are just roasting her.
This woman sucks!
She sounds like a bigot!
Hey, what's Germany ever done wrong?
So they find all her social media and they start attacking it,
and then she's got to make that private.
And the backlash got so bad, by sheer f***ing coincidence,
this young woman, who's a teenager, who just happens to be blonde,
and just happens to share the exact same legal name as Tipsy,
she starts getting harassed.
I have had to go as far as to delete everything off my Facebook and change my name.
And during all this, someone figures out where Tipsy works,
and they show the video to her corporate bosses over at this RX company she works at.
They not only fired her over this video,
they issued an official apology to anyone she hurt.
And all this happened on a New Jersey transit, so shout out to New Jersey.