I close my eyes and I can see a world that's waiting up for me
that I call my own
Through the dark, through the door, through where no one's been before
but it feels like home
They can say, they can say it all sounds crazy
They can say, they can say I've lost my mind
I don't care, I don't care, so call me crazy
We can live in a world that we design
Cause every night I lie in bed, the brightest colors fill my head
A million dreams are keeping me awake
I think of what the world could be, a vision of the one I see
A million dreams is all it's gonna take
A million dreams for the world we're gonna make
There's a house we can build, every room inside is filled
with things from far away
Special things I compile, each one there to make you smile
on a rainy day
They can say, they can say it all sounds crazy
They can say, they can say we've lost our minds
I don't care, I don't care if they call us crazy
Run away to a world that we design
Every night I lie in bed, the brightest colors fill my head
A million dreams are keeping me awake
I think of what the world could be, a vision of the one I see
A million dreams is all it's gonna take
A million dreams for the world we're gonna make
However big, however small, let me be part of it all
Share your dreams with me
You may be right, you may be wrong, but say that you'll bring me along
To the world you see, to the world I close my eyes and see
I close my eyes and see
Every night I lie in bed, the brightest colors fill my head
A million dreams are keeping me awake
I think of what the world could be, a vision of the one I see
A million dreams is all it's gonna take
A million dreams for the world we're gonna make
For the world we're gonna make