I am flesh and I am bone
Rise up, ting ting, like glitter and gold
I got fire in my soul
Rise up, ting ting, like glitter
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Like glitter and gold
Like glitter
Do you walk in the valley of kings?
Do you walk in the shadow of men
Who sold their lives to a dream?
Do you ponder the manner of things?
In the dark
The dark, the dark, the dark
I am flesh and I am bone
Rise up, ting ting, like glitter and gold
I got fire in my soul
Rise up, ting ting, like glitter
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Like glitter and gold
Like glitter
Do you walk in the meadow of spring?
Do you talk to the animals?
Do you hold their lives from a string?
Do you ponder the manner of things?
In the dark
The dark, the dark, the dark
I am flesh and I am bone
Rise up, ting ting, like glitter and gold
I got fire in my soul
Rise up, ting ting, like glitter
I am flesh and I am bone
Rise up, ting ting, like glitter and gold
I got fire in my soul
Rise up, ting ting, like glitter
Cause everybody in the back room's spinnin' out
You don't remember what you're askin' for
And everybody in the front room's trippin' out
You left your bottle at the door
Cause everybody in the back room's spinnin' out
You don't remember what you're askin' for
And everybody in the front room's trippin' out
You left your bottle at the door
I am flesh and I am bone or ice
Ding ding, life glitter and gold
I've got fire in my soul as I'm
Ding ding, life glitter
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Life glitter and gold
Life glitter
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Life glitter and gold
Life glitter