Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ooh
This is everything I did and I
Wait, don't tell me
Heaven is a place on Earth
I wish I could rewind all the times that I didn't
Show you what you really were
What you really were
Wait, you held me
I wish that I put you first
I was wrong I admit
None from the kids while you were slippin' through my fingertips
Takin' every breath away
With all of the mistakes I've made
From all the letters that I say
This is everything I didn't say
I wish I could have made you stay
And I'm the only one to blame
I know that it's a little too late
This is everything I didn't say
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ooh
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ooh
This is everything I didn't say
Wake me up now
And tell me this is all a bad dream
All the songs that I wrote
All the wrongs that I hoped would erase from your memory
Oh, teen or two
A broken and empty heart
That was I should have bought
All the hours I lost
Wish I could bring it back to the start
Taking every breath away
With all the mistakes I've made
From all the letters that I've saved
This is everything I didn't say
I wish I could have made you stay
And I'm the only one to blame
I know that it's a little too late
This is everything I didn't say
I hope you know
You are just right
To make this right
Whoa, whoa
Someday I'm sure
We'll pass each other by
Until that time
Taking every breath away
With all the mistakes I've made
From all the letters that I've saved
This is everything I didn't say
I wish I could have made you stay
And I'm the only one to blame
I know that it's a little too late
This is everything I didn't say
Oh, oh, oh