Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah You can be the peanut butter to my jelly
You can be the butterflies I feel in my belly You can be the captain and I can be your first
mate You can be the chills that I feel on our first
date You can be the hero and I can be your side
You can be the cake You can be the tear that I cry if we ever split
You can be the rain from the cloud when it's storming
Or you can be the sun when it shines in the morning
Don't know if I could ever be without you, cause boy you complete me
And in time I know that we'll both see that we're all we need
Cause you're the apple to my pie You're the straw to my berry
You're the smoke to my high And you're the one I wanna marry
Cause you're the one for me And I'm the one for you
You take the boat, the bus And we're the perfect two
We're the perfect two We're the perfect two
Baby me and you We're the perfect two
You can be the princess and I can be your princess
You can be the sweet tooth I can be the dentist
You can be the shoes and I can be the laces You can be the heart that I spill on the pages
You can be the vodka and I can be the chaser You can be the pencil and I can be the paper
You can be as cold as the winter weather But I don't care as long as we're together
Don't know if I could ever be without you, cause boy you complete me
And in time I know that we'll both see that we're all we need
Cause you're the apple to my pie You're the straw to my berry
You're the smoke to my high And you're the one I wanna marry
Cause you're the one for me And I'm the one for you
You take the boat, the bus And we're the perfect two
We're the perfect two We're the perfect two
Baby me and you We're the perfect two
You know that I'll never doubt you And you know that I'll think about you
And you know I can't live without you, no
I love the way that you smile And maybe in just a while
I can see me walk on the aisle Cause you're the apple to my pie
You're the straw to my berry You're the smoke to my high
And you're the one I wanna marry Cause you're the one for me
And I'm the one for you You take the boat, the bus
And we're the perfect two We're the perfect two
We're the perfect two Baby me and you
We're the perfect two