Baby I'm playing on you tonight, hunt you down eat your life
Just like animals, animals, like animals, balls
Maybe you think that you can hide, I can smell your symphonies
Baby I'm paying, show what you try to do to me
It's like we can't stop, we're enemies
But we get a little bit of insight into you, yeah
You're like a drug that's killing me, I cut you out entirely
But I get so high but I'm inside of you
Yeah you can start over, you can run free
You can find another visionless sea
You can pretend it's meant to be
But you can't stay away from me
I can still hear you making that sound
Taking me down, rolling underground
You can pretend that it was me, but no
Oh, baby I'm playing on you tonight, hunt you down eat your life
Just like animals, animals, like animals, balls
Maybe you think that you can hide, I can smell your symphonies
Baby I'm paying, so if I run it's not enough
You're still in my head forever, sir
So you can do what you wanna do, hey
I love your lies, I'll eat them up
But don't deny the animal
Becomes alive and I'm inside of you
Yeah you can start over, you can run free
You can find another visionless sea
You can pretend it's meant to be
But you can't stay away from me
I can still hear you making that sound
Taking me down, rolling underground
You can pretend that it was me, but no
Oh, baby I'm playing on you tonight, hunt you down eat your life
Just like animals, animals, like animals, balls
Maybe you think that you can hide, I can smell your symphonies
Baby I'm, don't tell no lie, lie, lie, lie
You can't deny, nah, nah, nah
That peace inside, side, side, side
Yeah, yeah, yeah
No girl, no lie, no lie, no lie
You can't deny, you can't deny
That peace inside, side, side, side
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah
Just like animals, animals, like animals, no
Just like animals, animals, like animals, yeah
Baby I'm playing on you tonight, hunt you down eat your life
Just like animals, animals, like animals, balls
Baby you think that you can hide, I can smell your symphonies
Baby I'm, don't tell no lie, lie, lie, lie
You can't deny, nah, nah, nah
That peace inside, side, side, side
Yeah, yeah, yeah
No girl, no lie, no lie, no lie
You can't deny, nah, nah, nah
That peace inside, side, side, side
Yeah, yeah, yeah